Letters to Josephine D. Siebert, 1943-1945
Connecticut Historical Society
Letters to Josephine D. Siebert
1943-1945
Connecticut Historical Society, Hartford, Connecticut
Siebert, George W.
2 boxes
Biographical Sketch
George W. Siebert was a golf professional at country clubs in the Hartford, Connecticut area before he entered the U.S. Marines in 1943. He left for the Pacific in September 1944. Upon his return to West Hartford, he again worked at country clubs as a manager and golf professional.
Scope and Content
The collection consists entirely of letters written by Siebert to his wife Josephine in West Hartford, Connecticut. They are arranged chronologically.
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions on access to the collection.
Accruals
The collection is closed.
Subject Headings
Personal Names
Siebert, George W., 1907-1962.; Siebert, Josephine D.
Subjects
Tokyo Rose.; World War --1939-1945.
Contents:
- Papers
  - Letters, 1943-April 1944 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Letters, May 1944 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Letters, August - September 1944 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Letters, October - November 1944 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Letters, December 1944 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Letters, January - February 1945 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Letters, March - April 1945 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Letters, May 1945 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Letters, June 1945 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Letters, July 1945 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Letters, August 1-12, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Letters, August 14-31, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Letters, September 2-17, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Letters, September 19-October 22, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Letters, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)